(Leonard:)...things between you and me
have been going pretty quick.
- And?
- It's just a little scary.
(Steph:)Well, yeah, but scary good, right?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
(Leonard:)When is scary not good?
(Leonard:)- But... Okay. Um, I have feelings, right?
- Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)Okay, and it's perfectly okay to express
those feelings, right?
Of course. Why don't you tell me
what you're feeling?
Okay, well, I ju... I think it's important
to remember that we move...
(Leonard:)...at a pace that is our speed and...
(Leonard:)Oh, shoot, I had it.
(Steph:)Okay, how about this?
How about I tell you what I'm feeling?
(Leonard:)What's that?
(Leonard:)Really? Right now?
- Why not?
- I just ate.
(Leonard:)Aren't you supposed to wait an hour?